Tile ringer song x2
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky?
I believe in tomorrow if we triumph!
Hey!
Come on, let's go everybody.
Oh, emos Saru the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go baby baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
Come on, let's go everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Let's go, baby, baby, oh
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
C'mon let's go everybody.
Oh we share the music.
C'mon let's go baby baby.
Oh we share the one world.
Oh as we chase we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times, show us that smile.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go, beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
I know that you are there,
just on the other side.
Wait there for me, soon
it will be you and I.
Then let us go, beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Hold on, you guys doing okay?
Thanks for the help there, Straw
Hat Yeah, thank you, Luffy-Chen.
Sure thing.
You guys done with yours?
Indeed.
You guys really are
amazing, you know that?
Thanks to your food, I'm
fighting on a full stomach.
Those guys didn't know what hit him.
Oh, man.
We didn't stand a chance back there.
We're not ready for a 300 million bounty.
Yeah, yeah, you might be right.
But just think about how many big
shots are on the archipelago right now.
We can at least back one of them.
can't we?
I'm so perplexed.
What in the world is going on?
We're being bombarded with
bounty hunters left and right.
That's three times
we've been ambushed now.
And the taste testing, oh,
sorry, I mean souvenir shops.
They've all disappeared.
Yeah,
it's kind of spooky seeing all these empty
buildings and no people walking around.
Seems like a sketchy location for a
coding mechanic.
You, you gotta keep in mind
how huge this archipelago is.
The government can't Keep a
watchful eye on all of it, you know.
The Marines won't even go
anywhere near this place.
Here, take a look.
A map of the islands?
It covers the whole archipelago with
the groves grouped into clusters of ten.
The borders aren't as clear-cut
in reality, of course.
For example, these are all the
areas we've passed through so far.
This is Grove 16.
It's part of Cluster 20.
Groves 1 through 29 are more or
less known as the Lawless area.
That's why the place is crawling
with so many bounty hunters.
And you couldn't have mentioned
that before we left the dock?
If I'd known that, I would have
let Zoro or Sanji come instead!
Don't worry, it's fine.
Our destination, Grove 13,
is just around the corner.
Oh, my gosh, Chopper Chin, you and
Skeleton Chin were really cool back there.
Oh, shut up.
That doesn't make me
feel better, you jerk.
I'm blushing so hard,
even my ears are red.
Oh, no, it's gone.
All right, here we are.
We made it in one piece.
That's the shop there
on top of that big root.
Let's hope they're still open.
It's been ten years since
the last time I was here.
Hey, Kuma, is this boat-coding mechanic
friend of yours a fish man, too?
You know, that's a good question.
Papagu and I haven't met him.
I've heard he's the absolute
best there is, though.
Oh, I thought you guys knew him.
Well, I guess we'll see.
This place is called
Shockey's Rip-Off Bar?
Hachi, I've got a sneaking suspicion
they're planning on ripping us off.
This coding mechanic isn't going to
beat us up and take our money, is he?
No, not at all.
They're good people.
I've known them since I was
no bigger than you, Papa Goo.
You didn't say this place was a bar.
Well, it looks like
they're still in business.
Rayleigh, Chaka!
Oh hey come on in what can i get for you?
Hold on is that really you Hatchan
i haven't seen you in ages you i know
sorry it's been so long Chaka me too
it's been at least 10 years hasn't it?
Make yourselves comfortable i won't be
another minute i just need to collect
some money these boys don't owe me
yeah sure take your time thanks son!
Really so you gave up the
pirate life hot chum yeah a lot
happened well i'm proud of you
an honest life is the best life
gotta say it's not too often
that you come across a mermaid
above water like this so Kuma
are you hot chon's girlfriend?
No i'm sorry but no hot chon's great and
all but no i'm way too young to get married
that's not what girlfriend
means Kuma works
with me at my fried octopus fritter stand.
Oh, is that all?
Hey, that reminds me.
Can I get you guys some...
One compliment, Chaka.
These boiled beans are delicious.
They're raiding the fridge!
Goofy, Brooke, no!
Stop before she rips you up! It's okay.
You go right ahead.
Wait.
I've got something you'll like,
too, here.
Cotton candy?
Oh, wow, thank you! Well, of course.
And that'll just be 100,000 berries.
But I...
I don't have that fun.
No, honey, it was just a joke.
I wouldn't charge friends of Hot John's
and I sure wouldn't rip them off.
Really?
How did you know that's Topper's favorite
food, lady? It was easy. You're Monkey D.
Luffy, right?
Whoa, hey, you know who I am?
Of course.
Everyone's talking about your crew.
And I work to stay well-informed.
Oh, you hear that, Luffy?
You're famous! Although,
I didn't know you had a
skeleton in your crew,
or that skeletons were
capable of moving and talking.
Here, that should be
warm enough. Thank you.
I read an article on you guys recently.
It was about the Annie's lobby incident.
I'm curious how much is true.
Did you guys really pick a
fight with the world government?
Ah, who cares?
It's a long, boring story.
Not much for bragging, huh?
You must be a big shot
One thing I was curious about Are you
related to the naval officer monkey D.
Garp? I sure am.
Garp's my grandpa That's what I thought.
A long time ago, he used to
chase me all over the sea. What?
There was a time when Chaka was a
notorious pirate herself Whoa, really?
Yep, it's the truth.
But I washed my hands
of it 40 years ago now!
Wait, 40 years?
How old are you, lady?
Old enough,
but these days I just get my kicks
from cheering on rookies like you guys.
Which brings us to why we're here.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Don't waste your breath.
I already know the whole story.
You and Kuma trekked up
on land and made the long,
uncomfortable journey to
the shop in order to help
Monkey and his crew here
get their ship coated.
Does that about sum it up?
Yeah, that was delicious! Try this.
So long story short, you have a
coat job for Rayleigh, don't you?
You?
Yeah, you got it.
Well, I hate to tell you,
but he's not here right now.
Huh?
Your mechanic's not here, but we're
trying to get down to Fishman Island!
I can guarantee you he's still
on the archipelago, at least.
Your best bet would probably be to search
for him in the bars or gambling houses.
Eh, it'd be easier to just
wait until he gets back.
Sure, of course.
You can wait.
He'll be back eventually, but
he's been gone for half a year.
Half a year?!
I'm sure he's shacked up with
some girl he met at a bar.
Can't really say I'm
too worried about him.
It's just natural behavior for
an old ex-pirate to disappear.
They go exploring and take
their time coming back.
Wait, you're saying the
mechanic was a pirate too?
That's right.
Well, that's certainly a conundrum.
But if he's not here, then I suppose we
have no choice but to find him ourselves.
Can you perhaps tell us which groves
we should start searching first?
Let's see.
If I had to guess,
I'd say you're most likely to find him
somewhere between Grove 1 and Grove 29.
He's quite notorious.
He can't relax if there's a
risk of running into the Navy.
So that's your best bet.
But if that place doesn't
work out, try Sabo Odi Park.
He likes it there.
The amusement park?
Yeah, that's where we're looking first!
Kuma, cut it out!
Amusement park!
Anyway, make sure you're careful
wherever you end up looking for him.
According to my network of contacts,
you've got some infamous company out there.
With your arrival on the
Sabo Odi Archipelago,
there are now 11 people with bounties
exceeding 100 million berries on the groves.
There are 11 people with
bounties that high? That's right.
Adding Roro Noah and Monkey
here to the list, you've got 11.
So there are nine others.
You had a choice to make when
you crossed the Grand Line.
There were seven sea routes
that would lead you here.
And after you picked one, you followed
your Log Pose the rest of the way, right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, naturally, these other pirates picked
one of the six routes you chose not to.
And trust me, they went through just
as much trouble as you did to get here.
It doesn't matter which route you take.
You eventually hit the red line.
And everyone winds up on this archipelago
with the hopes of getting
past that giant wall.
It's a bit crazy that
all of the world's best
rookies managed to show
up here at the same time,
though.
And such a notorious lot at that.
At the top, you've got Kidd,
yourself, Hawkins, Drake, and Law.
I'm guessing you must
have seen these other
names in the newspapers
alongside your own.
I don't read newspapers.
Information is a weapon.
It'd be a smart move to at least
learn the names of your rivals.
Okay, so there was Kidd, Hawkins,
and, uh, it was Drake, right?
Her appetite is terrifying.
How could she even fit all
that food into her body?
More!
Bring more food!
What a vulgar woman.
Just the cider has making
me lose my appetite.
Go wire jaw shut.
That's not a good idea father
We're right by Navy headquarters.
The last thing we need to cause a scene
Capone gang bag.
He has a bounty of a hundred and thirty
eight million berries on his head
Where's the rest of the food?
Hurry and bring it before I starve
Boss, the waiter swears they're
cooking it as fast as they can.
It's on the way.
Well, it's not fast enough, damn it!
Pizza! More pizza!
Jewelry Bonnie, a .k .a. The Glutton.
Her bounty, 140 million berries.
Right.
We'll have your food for you immediately.
I'm so, so sorry.
You little...
Leave him be.
You can't be serious, Captain.
I'm soaked in spaghetti.
Look at my clothes.
Such was the fate of your pants.
I apologize for my man threatening you.
Taking a life on this day will
only bring our crew bad fortune.
Basil Hawkins, the magician.
He has a bounty of 249 million berries.
What the?
They're fighting!
Could you really not wait for the
other side of the red line to fight me?
Just curious, but do you
have any clue who I am?
The Sea Roar, Scratchman Apu.
The bounty on his head
is 198 million berries.
All I know is you wouldn't
stop staring at me.
Captain, please don't do it!
You are one creepy-looking bastard.
Why don't you just let me
put you out of your misery?
Eustass Captain Kit.
His bounty, 315 million berries.
The mad bone's on a rampage!
We gotta get out of here
before he levels the place!
If you want to go wild,
save it for the new world!
Red Flag Diaz Drake.
He's got a bounty of 222 million berries.
I can wait.
Are you the fallen Navy officer, Drake?
Mad Monk Uruge.
He has a bounty worth 108 million berries.
You should get down on your knees and
thank Drake for your life, masked man.
The Massacre Soldier, killer.
His bounty, 162 million berries.
Damn, it was just starting to get good.
Hey, Drake, I'm curious.
How many people have you killed?
Trafalgar Law, the Surgeon of Death.
His bounty is 200 million berries.
As you know, a countless number of
pirate crews have entered the Grand Line,
but only a handful have made it this far.
The Grand Line is basically an
enormous tournament of survival,
regardless of which path
they took to get here.
The ones that made it are
the cream of the crop.
I'd even go so far as to say
that one of them might go
on to become the leader of the
next generation of pirates!
So fair warning!
With this many rookies passing
the red line at the same time,
Things are bound to get
quite ugly in the new world.
Also,
in case you're wondering why Captain
Kidd's bounty is so much higher than yours?
It's because he has no qualms
with attacking innocent civilians.
Not very charming, huh?
I prefer you boys.
You can count on my support.
I'll be cheering for you all the way
Thanks, but I gotta be honest with you.
I'm just trying to have fun
But you do have me a little
afraid for the old coding
mechanic pirate guy this
town sounds pretty rough.
Oh you've got nothing to worry about.
Trust me Rayleigh's all right.
He's a hundred times stronger than you
did she say a hundred times
you ready chomper yeah just so you
know i'm sure the navy is aware that
all you up and coming heavy-hitting
pirates have made landfall here i'd
keep an eye out for anything suspicious
if i were you now that's not good
so you're saying they could strike
at any time from out of nowhere Yes,
but you might be in luck
in addition to the usual
troublemakers around
these parts With all the
other pirates landing
here at the same time Navy
headquarters probably has
its hands full right now
Unless something especially
problematic happens
the Navy won't waste major
military resources on
checking it out In other
words keep your heads down
try not to cause any trouble
and you should be fine.
Okay?
Sure I understand.
Thanks a lot.
You are a real big help
I'm telling you they were crazy strong
sounds like you had a rough time?
So what's this proposition of yours right
I'm sorry sir you see
master peterman I think
the Girl with Straw Hat luffy might be a
mermaid I noticed something
when I saw her before
After she fell to the ground her shoe came
off when it did I saw
a fin instead of a foot
But these strong companions you mentioned
sound like they could be a lot of trouble!
Nonetheless, a mermaid spotted on dry
land is certainly a golden opportunity.
They're impossible to catch in open water.
I appreciate all the info.
You came to the right man.
And for that info, you can
have 10 % of her selling price.
Well, we were really hoping for 20.
I mean, 10 % is plenty!
We're here!
Savoni Park! Yay!
Oh, man!
This place looks fun!
Focus!
Remember why we're here!
I remember!
That lady said this is where
we should look for him, right?
Only if we couldn't find
him in the lawless area.
Ah!
It's so fair as well!
Have you ever seen it
from this class before?
All right! Listen up!
It's fun time!
You're not even trying to find him!
Yay!
Kuma, you are forbidden
to step inside that place!
Absolutely forbidden!
My, what a lovely and
leisurely ride this is!
Oh, and look at this view, how relaxing!
Yes, gentle rides like
this one are more my style.
This way I can still enjoy the
lovely view without having to.
Faster, faster, faster!
Faster! Faster!
What the heck is wrong with you people?
Who in the right minds
would spend that hard?
Are you crazy?
Who's going to pay for all this damage?
Oh, wow!
We're so high up!
Look, over here, the ocean!
Cool!
It's all so beautiful!
It's the most amazing
thing I've ever seen!
Hey, what's the crying
all about? It's just...
I've dreamed of this moment
ever since I was a little girl.
I've never been so high
up in the air before!
I'll always remember this day.
Thank you so much!
I couldn't have come here without you.
Hatchan and Papaku only let me come to this
place because I knew you'd keep me safe.
You.
I gotta admit, I'm probably every
bit as happy as Kuma is right now.
Every mer-child and fish kid
dreams of coming to this place,
though not many of us get to really do it.
So high! So high!
So very high!
Let's ride this one!
Gondola!
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go! Ah!
Ah!
Come on!
I'm so excited! Come on!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
High Priest-A-Rouge, look over there.
My, my, what a sight.
A celestial dragon, huh?
to think they'd wander around the
lawless area without a care in the world.
I don't like this, but our only choice
is to kneel and let him pass on by.
Sharia and father left
me, and in this cesspool,
where did they wander off to this time?
Well, we do know their final
destination, so rest easy.
We'll meet up with them soon enough.
Slow as a turtle you can't crawl
gracefully, but a horrible ride!
Hey you what are you doing there?
Why are you moving?
You should be still and proud
I'm so very sorry.
Please overlook this, sir.
This man needs urgent care.
We're reaching against time.
The hospital is just up ahead.
Yes, I see.
This is very bad indeed.
Well, in that case, you must be swift.
And put him out of his misery!
I beg you, stop! Oh, no!
Look at that.
Now that is one selfish noble.
Tell me, what's more important?
Showing me courtesy or
a mere commoner's life?
Every commoner owes their very
existence to the Celestial Dragons.
It's settled.
I'm making you my new wife.
Very good, sir.
I shall make arrangements to send her to
the Holy Land as your thirteenth wife.
By the by, I've grown quite weary
of wives one through five lately.
Have them sit back to
live with the commoners.
Of course, sir, as you wish.
Please don't do this!
I beg you!
What are you doing?
She's my fiancée!
You can't just come here and...
How dare you speak to me
when you should be kneeling!
Marie.
You murderer!
How could you?
Somebody help him!
Help him, please!
He's going to die!
Someone, please!
These celestial dragons are
as wicked as the rumors say.
What was that?
You would have these
people act out against me?
Please let go of me! Stop it!
Take her ahead to the
harbor for me. Yes, sir.
Who's that?
I recognize him, Captain.
That guy's Pirate Hunter
Zoro from the East Blue.
Why is he walking right down
the middle of the street?
Don't he know you don't
do that around here?
He's going to cause a lot of trouble.
Hey, what's the matter?
Do you need some directions or something?
What in the hell does he think he's doing?
A kid?
Oh!
Big Brother!
Why'd you have to die?
Why'd you leave me? Nooo!
Just stay still, tough guy.
Oh!
Big Brother!
Why'd you stand up to a Celestial Dragon?
You know they can only end in death!
I guess I actually sought him, huh?
Thought for sure he
dodged at the last second,
but oh, well, must be imagining things.
Well, whatever.
As long as he's dead.
What the heck were you
thinking attacking a
celestial dragon like that
you'll bring admirals?
Here what's with all this
tomato juice it's to make you
look dead and unless you want
to be that way for real mr.
troublemaker you better obey the unwritten
pirate rules what are you
talking About hey? Wait a minute!
There was a kid here.
Where'd she go?
Don't get the rest of us
caught up in your trouble!
Are you messed up in the head?
No, I'm fine.
I didn't hit my head.
You numbskull!
I'm talking about the inside! Jeez!
What a dumbass!
How have you survived this long?
Well?
Thanks to jewelry!
Barney over there!
We managed to avoid the
worst case scenario!
That man is pirate on Azoro! A member?
of the Straw Hat Pirates.
I heard their crew was kind of
wild, but attacking a dragon!
and in a public street in broad daylight?
That's plain bonkers.
It's only natural that he was saved.
I didn't see the shadow of
death upon him at this time.
I felt his bloodlust.
That guy will cut you down
without a second thought.
He's a real monster.
A bounty of 120 million berries.
Doesn't seem like a lackey, but
he's number two on the Straw Hats.
I guess that goes to show
the caliber of his captain.
Right, so, where's the
nearest hospital? Hospital?
This man needs a doctor.
He took a bullet. What? Forget him.
He's a total stranger.
You've got to be kidding me.
A pirate helping out some random guy?
Never seen that before.
I saw something when I went into town.
These bubble bicycle
things were flying around.
Yeah, I saw those, too. Pretty cool, huh?
We should buy a couple.
I bet you those bikes
have a real smooth ride.
The snail.
It's probably Nami.
Click.
Hello, my beautiful Nami! Sanji!
Sanji and Chopper, listen to me!
Basically, they had so many kinds of ice
cream, we got caught up and made a mistake!
Slow down, you're not making any sense.
No, Sanji, it's terrible! Terrible!
What are we gonna do?
I don't know what you're saying calm
down just start over what's going on
We don't even have a clue what kidnapter.
This place is gigantic.
We need to split up and start...
Don't move.
Tell me exactly where you are.
We'll come and meet you there.
But we...
We know some experts when it comes
to this sort of thing, remember?
I'm calling in the Flying Fish Riders.
What?
Yahoo!
Handsome's here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I mean, Duval's here.
So are we!
How are you, young Master Blackleg?
Angry, because you fish
riders took too long!
We're not fish riders anymore,
young Master, you remember?
We're the Rosie Life Riders now.
You're freaking annoying, okay?
That's what you are!
It's our mermaid friend.
She got kidnapped in Sabaody Park.
I called you to help us find her.
Not kidnappers?
How horrible!
They sound like devious villains!
You guys were kidnappers
too, like what, yesterday?
They say it takes a thief to catch one.
So here we are.
Are you guys up for this?
But of course.
We shall do our very best to serve you.
Your wish is our command.
Can we really trust these guys?
Oh, and by the by, before I came here, I
showed off my new looks to some ladies.
I wasn't quite the success
that I imagined I would be.
Well, I can fix your
face, but not your brain.
Or your annoying personality.
But that's all right.
I'll help you out.
Don't you worry.
We just need to find your mermaid
friend before she gets sold, right?
You got it.
Since you're from around here,
I figure you must know the
archipelago better than us.
Why, of course we do.
Sabo Odi is our backyard.
We know all the ins and outs.
You won't find a better
tour guide than us.
Okay, hop on.
We're taking the flying fish?
You bet we are.
Right, ready when you are.
Right.
Uh, how do you guys plan on finding her?
Now, don't fret.
Those of a trade know each other's ways,
and we were once kidnappers as well.
I can think of a few groups
already that might be responsible.
First off,
we'll take a quick cruise
across the groves and pick up
the rest of your crew so they
can help with the search.
In the meantime,
we'll try and find out which
kidnappers grabbed your mermaid friend.
Let's go!
Full speed ahead!
Yeah!
I hope this works out.
Sanji, what now?
It's gonna be okay.
Just stay right there
and don't move an inch.
I'll send someone there to get you.
Okay.
Calic.
Luffy!
Sanji says not to go!
Just to be safe,
we should still wait here instead
of breaking up the group even more.
Don't you think, Brooke?
Let me put it this way Sanji gave us very
specific instructions
to stay here and wait
for someone to come
pick us up and no matter
what we do our wait will be just as long?
Hey, head, we made it to
Sabaody Park. What's next?
Find the rest of the Straw Hats
and pick up one member each.
Right.
They were supposed to wait by public
transponder snail number five,
which should be right here.
Yeah, there they are.
See, on the bench.
It looks like Brooke and Chopper.
All right, you guys, we're ready to go.
Hurry up, let's...
Why are you two so relaxed?
This is serious!
Let's go!
Operation Save Kuma at
all costs is underway!
Yes!
Let's go all out!
No relaxing!
But he got mad at us!
I knew it then, I regret it now!
Just a little bit, but I regret it!
Keep on the lookout for every
kidnapping team on the archipelago!
It's gotta be one of them, so
it's only a matter of time!
And I know the other Straw Hats ran
off, but we still got to find them, too.
Roger.
Let's split up. Ride!
We're betting our pride on this.
You better not let the young master down.
Do this fast and do it right, okay?
That should be good enough.
Good enough for who?
And can't you do something
about this slow-ass cow?
If I'd have known it was like
this, I would have got on a fish.
What?
You said I'm handsome?
Not even close.
Also, you're the head of your gang.
Why are you stuck on the slowest
ride when everyone else can fly?
Why would you say something like that?
Of course I'm the most
handsome person on the team.
There's no competition.
Just shut up and step on it, okay?
Yes, young master.
Do you swear no one came
here to sell a mermaid?
Yeah, yeah, I swear it.
No one today.
Stop it, Straw Hat.
It'll only be harder on
us if you cause trouble.
Octoguy, let's look around the shop.
Okay.
Hey.
Did you guys have any luck?
No, looks like he was
telling the truth. Jamie!
Come on, Straw Hat.
We're gonna have to look somewhere else.
Hey, I just remembered.
Now that you mention
it, I do have a mermaid.
For real? Do you mean it?
Yeah, but only one.
This pretty little thing here.
Her name's Mari.
If you like her, I'll
cut you guys a good deal.
Don't you want to take me home?
There's no way in hell that's a mermaid!
I saw him in the shop just a second ago.
It's really hard to breathe in here.
Hey!
Kuma!
Where are you?
You, don't lose hope.
Maybe she hasn't been sold yet.
We just gotta figure out
which kidnappers grabbed her.
Hey, check it out.
That guy's Straw Hat Luffy
from the East Blue, isn't he?
He's shorter than I thought.
This is all my fault.
The amusement park is the number one
spot for kidnappers to pick people up.
I knew they'd be on the lookout for a
mermaid like her but I didn't do a thing.
Whoa they've got all
kinds of ice cream here.
What flavor do you want? Hold on.
I gotta go see it for myself.
I'll be right back.
Kuma you wait here.
Yeah. Okay.
But get something yummy for me too.
All right.
I'm never going to see her again, and the
last thing I said was about ice cream.
It's terrible.
I never should have let her
go to that amusement park.
What was I thinking?
It's just, I've dreamed of this
moment ever since I was a little girl.
I've never been so high
up in the air before.
I'll always remember this day.
Thank you so much.
You didn't do anything wrong.
She was really happy we got to go.
It's nobody's fault it
turned out like that.
You don't get it.
Truth is It's a terrible idea for fishmen
and merfolk to come to this place at all.
But hachi he wanted to help you
guys after what you did for us.
And I felt the same way.
Papagu, don't say anymore.
We're stuck like this
either way You might as
well tell me why it's so
bad for you to come here.
What's the big deal?
The kidnappers.
They're not the only enemies
Kuma and Hachi have in Sabo Odi.
In fact You might say everyone in
the whole archipelago is their enemy
Two hundred years ago?
Yes, it's more recent
than you would think.
But things used to be quite terrible here.
The fishmen and merfolk races
were considered the same as fish,
and humans all over the world
persecuted them in every possible way.
They were seen as lesser than human,
and they were treated as such.
That's a surprise since
they're so strong. Perhaps.
But strength in numbers is greater still,
and they were treated cruelly by everyone,
until the world government declared
friendly relations with Fishman Island.
Slavery is another relic
from that unfortunate past,
and human trafficking is still
very alive on this archipelago.
In fact, it may even be condoned.
If such a deplorable
tradition still remains?
It wouldn't surprise me if
they continue to discriminate.
against Fishman and Murfolk here as well.
Persecution?
You're a fool if you can't see
this place for what it really is.
The human trafficking is
just the icing on the cake.
But I should know better.
So I blame myself for not
stopping Kuma when we got here.
That explains the disguises.
They didn't want people to know
that they weren't human, huh?
Let's just hope these fears
of mine are unfounded.
Robin! Carol!
Franky!
Did you just call me Carol?
What's wrong with you?
Get on the flying fish quick!
Somebody kidnapped the mer-chick!
They took Kuma?
You're kidding me.
Kuma!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat.
I wanted to help, not cause more trouble.
This is a mess, you.
What are you guys talking about?
Stop apologizing.
There isn't anything to be sorry for.
All three of you are my friends now.
I don't care what happened.
We're in this together.
And we're going to rescue Kuma
no matter what, okay? Don't cry!
Straw Hat!
You mean it?
Hey guys what the good we
finally found you now get
up here I'll do guy can you
jump that high whoo yeah
All right I'm expecting some good results
this time worry you're gonna make a
Killing they'll love this one come by in a
few hours and we'll have your money Ready?
Looking forward to it.
Oh.
It's an honor to have you here, St.
Roswald and St. Shalria. Of course.
Could we refrain from kneeling
in the auction house, sir?
It would make our jobs very difficult.
That'll be fine.
We don't want a boring auction.
Ah, that's very generous of you.
Please, use the VIP seats.
My brother's certainly
taking his time getting here.
That's what the fool gets
for riding a sluggish human.
If you're going to ride
something, make it a fish man.
They may be filthy, but they're
ten times stronger than humans.
Celestial dragons.
Slaves.
Human shops.
That pirate?
Yeah, that's Captain
Kidd from the South Blue.
When the people in power
act this cruel and greedy,
it makes common criminals like us
look pretty humane by comparison.
When scum like that are the ones
writing the rules, it creates more scum.
They hate pirates, but they're
the ones who made them.
At least we're as endearing
as we are mean, right, killer?
Seems fair.
Agreed.
If we see someone interesting, you
think we should try and buy them?
Hey, boss, take a look. See that?
Well, I'll be damned.
That's Trafalgar Law from the North Blue.
Worth $200 million.
I've heard some pretty
ugly rumors about him.
He must be a fan of mine, too.
Disco!
We've got an incredible item today!
Oh, yes, I've already seen the giant.
He's nice.
Don't you worry, I'll make
sure it sells for a high price.
Speaking of which, are
the buy bidders ready?
No, not the giant!
We've got a mermaid!
and she's young, too.
This will be an auction for
the record books. Really?
Let me go!
You're hurting me!
Why are you doing this?
You're not getting away,
so you might as well stop flopping
like that, you stupid fish!
Now, now, let's not roughhouse.
Our important merchandise
quite so much, sorry, disco.
So this is the star of today's show?
Yes, sir.
This is just splendid.
She's not only young, she's lively.
She'll fetch a high price, indeed.
Who submitted her?
The hound pets, sir.
Of course, Peterman.
He always does fine work.
The flying Fish riders on the other hand
haven't turned in a thing this time.
Well, in any case, this is sure
to Be the biggest auction in ages.
You
dare make a face at me?
I can destroy you.
You're nothing but a fish.
Don't forget that I know.
She's awful, sir, but she's
valuable merchandise, like you said.
Yeah.
We need her in good shape
for the auction, at least.
Kick her in the stomach or somewhere
that's covered up by clothes?
Pajun is going to beat you up so bad.
Just wait and see.
You don't know when to shut
that filthy mouth, do you?
You there, give me that collar.
Oh, here, sir.
I'll put this on you myself, fish.
No!
Disco?
What happened? Are you okay? Dammit!
The auction's about to start!
Doctor! Get a doctor!
Hey, you.
I felt that.
You can't play dumb with
me, that Haki there.
It was yours, wasn't it?
Just who in the hell are you, old man?
Hmph.
I'm just a simple ship
Katorea. Nothing more.
What can I say?
I have a soft spot for young girls.
Though I may have overdone it a bit.
Thank you.